 const data = [ 
    {
        question : "There are ___ levels of heading in HTML",
        incorrectAnswers: ["Three", "Four" ,"Five" ],
        correctAnswer : "Six" 
    },
    {
        question : "The decimal range of network address for class B network is between",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                         "127-190",
                         "128-190",
                         "None of the above" ],
        correctAnswer : "128-191" 
    },
    {
        question : "What is the Full Form of the IMAP?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Internet Mails Access Protocol",
                            "Internet Memo Access Protocol" ,
                            "All of them" ],
        correctAnswer : "Internet Mail Access Protocol" 
    },
    {
        question : "What is the Full Form of the SPX?",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Sequence Packet Exchange", 
                            "Sequenced Packets Exchange",
                            "None of the above" ],
        correctAnswer : "Sequenced Packet Exchange" 
    },
    {
        question : " The Full form Of the MIME is:",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Multiple Internet Mail Extensions", 
                            "Multiple Internet Mails Extensions",
                            "None of the above" ],
        correctAnswer : "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions" 
    },
    {
        question : "The ___ at the bottom of your window provides you the status of how much percentage of the Web Page is loaded and how much is remaining.",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Program Indicator",
                            "Program Director" ,
                            "None of the above" ],
        correctAnswer : "Progress Indicator" 
    },
    {
        question : " ___ is widely known as the father of the World Wide Web",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Tom burners-lee", 
                            "Tom bruce-lee",
                            "Tim bruce-lee" ],
        correctAnswer : "Tim Berners-Lee" 
    },
    {
        question : "The Major components of the Web browser are ___",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Menu bar", 
                            "Tool bar",
                            "Location" ],
        correctAnswer : "All of the above" 
    },
    {
        question : "The leading bit pattern for the class c network is",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "0",
                            "10",
                            "101" ],
        correctAnswer : "None of the above" 
    },
    {
        question : "URL is an acronym for",
        incorrectAnswers: [
                            "Universal research locator", 
                            "Universal resource locator",
                            "Uniform research locator" ],
        correctAnswer : "Uniform Resource Locator" 
    },
]
export default data;